USB Memory Direct Privacy Policy
================================

At USB Memory Direct, we take it as our responsibility to protect every customer's personal information. This policy outlines how your information is handled and kept secure. When you send us personal information, it will be treated according to this policy.

This policy covers the USB Memory Direct corporate website and is applicable worldwide. It is possible that one of our subsidiaries will have its own policies that may be different. We advocate reading our privacy policy and those of any website you visit.

**Personal Data Gathering**

You will be told before we acquire any personal information from you, the purpose of which will always be apparent. The term “Personal Information” applies to any data that can be used to identify an individual, and includes, but is not limited to, name, postal or other physical address, credit or debit card information, occupation, email address, and any other data received by us in order to provide a service, deliver a product, or proceed with a transaction requested by one of our customers.

Examples of when we would collect personal information include:

* Registration on our website(s)
* Placement of a transaction or order with us
* Requests for service and support of our products or services
* Usage of certain features within our products or services
* Participation in an online survey
* Registration to membership programs or newsletter subscriptions

**Personal Data Usage**

Your personal information will only be utilized in the manner we specified when it was originally collected. It will not be used in a different manner without your knowledge and consent.

* Processing your orders and delivering the products and services requested
* Providing support and assistance for our products and services
* Providing current information on our latest product announcements, updates, enhancements, special offers, and other relevant information
* Providing the ability to register a personal profile and access protected content
* Providing customer feedback and support services
* Meeting contractual obligations

**Gathering Anonymous Data**

In some cases, USB Memory Direct may retrieve non-personal (aggregate or demographic) data using such methods as cookies. This is utilized to help understand and evolve the functionality and usefulness of our website(s).

As well, by using some of our products or services, anonymous information may be sent back to us, such as technical system information about your computer. This data is sent to us so that we can understand how users interact with our products, to help improve them, and to provide communication regarding the product and any available updates or upgrades.

**Personal Data and Sharing**

Your personal information may be shared within USB Memory Direct or any of our subsidiaries for the purposes of data processing or storage.

Your personal information may be shared with business partners, service vendors, authorized third-party agents, or contractors in order to provide a specifically requested service or transaction. This might include processing orders, credit card transactions, website hosting, event and seminar registration, or customer support. We would only provide third parties with the absolute minimum amount of data required to complete any requested service or transaction, while the third parties involved are forbidden from using such data other than for the limited cause of following through with the requested service or transaction.

We may respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process by disclosing your personal information and other related information, if required. It is also possible we may opt to exercise our legal rights or defend against any legal claims.

We may share personal information and any other additional data available in order to investigate, prevent, or take action in regard to suspected illegal activities, fraud, threats to other individuals, violations of USB Memory Direct's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

When using USB Memory Direct's website(s) you may be directed to content or functionality that is hosted by a third-party entity. This is usually part of hosting a special event, such as contests. When your information is gathered on behalf of USB Memory Direct exclusively, our privacy policy will be referenced on the site to define how your data is used. For other, non-USB Memory Direct sites, the privacy policy of that site will be referenced. Our policy is to require that information handling from these suppliers be consistent with our privacy and security procedures.

We will never sell or rent any customer's personal information to third parties for marketing purposes unless that customer has given us express authorization to do so. We will ask for consent by you before we use or share your personal information for any other purpose other than the reason you gave or as otherwise noted in this privacy policy. So that we may know your preferences, we require your action and responsibility, such as choosing an appropriate option, indicating your consent.

Google: We may use cookies in collaboration with Google for internal remarketing and advertising purposes. By using our website, you consent to the use of these cookies for these purposes within Google Ads, Google Analytics and Google reCAPTCHA. For more information on how your information is stored within the Google suite, please see [Google's Privacy & Terms.](https://policies.google.com/privacy#infocollect)

Microsoft Ads: We may use cookies in collaboration with Microsoft for internal remarketing and advertising purposes. By using our website, you consent to the use of these cookies for these purposes. For more information on how your information is stored within the Microsoft suite, please see [Microsoft's Privacy & Terms.](https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/privacy/)

Meta: We may use cookies in collaboration with Meta for internal remarketing and advertising purposes. By using our website, you consent to the use of these cookies for these purposes. For more information on how your information is stored within Meta, please see [Meta's Privacy & Terms.](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/policy/)

LiveChat: We may utilize cookies for our LiveChat feature, which gives us the ability to help website users in real time. For information on the cookies used by this widget, visit [LiveChat's privacy policy.](https://www.livechat.com/legal/privacy-policy/)

Session Tracking: We may use cookies to analyze website interaction, such as how you move and engage within our website. This information helps us identify and fix technical issues visitors may have. For more information on session tracking and how it is used, please see [HotJar's privacy policy.](https://www.hotjar.com/privacy/)

**Personal Data Security**

USB Memory Direct is deeply committed to the sustained security of any personal information you choose to share with us. Using a composite of industry-standard security technologies, procedures, and organizational policies, we will protect personal information from unauthorized access, usage, or disclosure.

When transferring sensitive data (for example, payment information) over the Internet, it is protected by utilizing Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption.

While striving to protect all your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of information that you send by Internet, phone, mail, or any other means of communication. It is recommended to take every measure to protect personal information from exposure while on the Internet. Be sure to change passwords often, create unique passwords, and use a secure browser with the latest updates.

**Keeping Information**

USB Memory Direct will not keep your personal data longer than is required to fulfill the purposes for which it was obtained or as is required by applicable laws or regulations.

**Cookies**

As with many sites on the Internet, USB Memory Direct utilizes technologies such as cookies, which give us the ability to make using our website(s) easier, more functional and more useful by providing you with a customizable experience that recognizes you upon return.

A cookie will not read personal data found on the hard disk or from cookies made by other websites. The only personal information a cookie keeps is that which you supply yourself to that website. If you accept our website(s) cookies, they may give us access to information about your browsing behavior, which may be utilized to personalize visits, track user traffic patterns, and merge such data once you register. This is done to determine how efficient our site is to our users and to help improve how it is navigated. Our website(s) should be able to be browsed without cookies enabled, however pages involving purchases or requiring a login and password require cookies and will not function if you have cookies disabled in your web browser.

**Outside Links**

The websites of USB Memory Direct and its subsidiaries may have links to third-party sites that we have no control over and are not covered by this privacy policy. It is advised to review the privacy policy of any sites you visit.

**Posting Information Publicly**

Any information that you submit publicly, such as in a forum or chat room, will be available for others to see, which may possibly include individuals both internal and external to our company who visit such areas. Please be aware that these individual areas may contain additional rules and provisions. The information that individuals post in these areas is of their own opinion and should not be taken as the views of USB Memory Direct.

**Personal Data Transfer**

It may be necessary to transfer your personal data within our company, to one of our subsidiaries, or to third-parties acting at our behest, such as for processing orders or storage.

**How to Unsubscribe**

You may request to unsubscribe from our newsletters by sending a letter, including name, address, email, and the title of the marketing material to:

USB Memory Direct  
Privacy Department  
1940 Harrison St #101  
Hollywood, FL 33020  
United States  

We will gladly remove your information from the requested mailing list, however we cannot prevent accidental mailings, such as may occur through multiple entries of the same information. Please allow up to 8 weeks for all mailings, online and physical, to cease.

**Contact for Questions/Comments**

If you have the need to contact us in regard to our privacy policy or have any questions about it, feel free to write us at [privacy@usbmemorydirect.com](mailto:privacy@usbmemorydirect.com)

**Revisions to this Privacy Policy**

We may alter or add on to this statement of policies at any time without notice. Returning to our website(s) after such a change is made will indicate your continued agreement with any revisions.

RECEIVE $50 OFF ON YOUR FIRST ORDER\*

Subscribe To Receive $50 Off

\*($500 min.) Cannot be combined with other discounts or offers.

 Sign Up!
